(Sheldon:)Amy has a fondness
for the comic strip Marmaduke.
(Leonard:)-And...?
-And I think I've got it.
Consider: A family possesses a dog
that is so large
(Sheldon:)and poorly disciplined,
he causes nothing but problems.
Why do they keep him?!
(Leonard:)Maybe they fell in love with him
as a puppy
(Leonard:)and didn't know how big
he was gonna be.
(Leonard:)Of course.
(Sheldon:)You know, why couldn't
she just like Ziggy? Yeah?
(Sheldon:)That thing's riddled with plot holes.
(Leonard:)Sorry, buddy.
(Sheldon:)I think she's a fan of Garfield
as well.
(CHUCKLES)
(Sheldon:)Oh, darn it, now so am I.
I'll see you later. I got to go watch
a stupid football game with Penny.
(Sheldon:)Wait, hang on.
You've spent time with Amy.
(Sheldon:)Can you think of anything
she's fond of
(Sheldon:)that has a bunch of flaws
she hasn't noticed?
I got to go.